{
  "isTheory": true,
  "openingRemarks": "Find the solution to the following equations",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(3w + 7 = 19 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3w + 7 &= 19 \\\\\n3w &= 19 - 7 \\\\\n3w &= 12 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3w}{3} &= \\dfrac{12}{3} \\\\\nw &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 19 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3w + 7\\) if \\(w=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3w + 7 &= 3(4) + 7 \\\\\n&= 12 + 7 \\\\\n&= 19\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2g - 13 = 3 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2g - 13 &= 3 \\\\\n2g &= 3 + 13 \\\\\n2g &= 16 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2g}{2} &= \\dfrac{16}{2} \\\\\ng &= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 3 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2g - 13\\) if \\(g=8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2g - 13 &= 2(8) - 13 \\\\\n&= 16 - 13 \\\\\n&= 3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(11 = 12 - q \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n11 &= 12 - q \\\\\n11 - 12 &= -q \\\\\n-1 &= -q \\\\\n\\dfrac{-1}{-1} &= \\dfrac{-q}{-1} \\\\\n1 &= q \\\\\nq &= 1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 11 = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(12 - q\\) if \\(q=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n12 - q &= 12 - 1 \\\\\n&= 11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10 = 7 - m \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10 &= 7 - m \\\\\n10 - 7 &= -m \\\\\n3 &= -m\\\\\n\\dfrac{3}{-1} &= \\dfrac{-m}{-1} \\\\\n-3 &= m \\\\\nm &= -1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 10 = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7 - m\\) if \\(m=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7 - m &= 7 - (-3) \\\\\n&= 7 + 3 \\\\\n&= 10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 = \\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 &= \\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3 \\\\\n-4 \\times 5 &= -4\\left(\\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3\\right) \\\\\n-20 &= z + 12 \\\\\n-20 - 12 &= z \\\\\n-32 &= z \\\\\nz &= -32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 5 = RHS </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3\\) if \\(z=-32\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{z}{-4} - 3 &= \\dfrac{-32}{-4} -3 \\\\\n&= 8 - 3 \\\\\n&= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4 = 6 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4 &= 6 \\\\\n3\\left(\\dfrac{a}{3}\\right) + 4 \\times 3 &= 6 \\times 3 \\\\\na + 12 &= 18 \\\\\na &= 18 - 12 \\\\\na &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 6 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4\\) if \\(a=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{a}{3} + 4 &= \\dfrac{6}{3} + 4 \\\\\n&= 2 + 4 \\\\\n&= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{h + 6}{5} = 2 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{h + 6}{5} &= 2 \\\\\n5 \\times \\dfrac{h+6}{5} &= 2 \\times 5 \\\\\nh + 6 &= 10 \\\\\nh &= 10 - 6 \\\\\nh &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 2 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{h+6}{5}\\) if \\(h=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{h+6}{5} &= \\dfrac{4+6}{5} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{10}{5} \\\\\n&= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{d - 8}{-2} = 12 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{d - 8}{-2} &= 12 \\\\\n-2 \\times \\dfrac{d-8}{-2} &= 12 \\times -2 \\\\\nd - 8 &= -24 \\\\\nd &= -24 + 8 \\\\\nd &= -16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 12 </div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{d-8}{-2}\\) if \\(d=-16\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{d-8}{-2} &= \\dfrac{-16-8}{-2} \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{-24}{-2} \\\\\n&= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8y + 3y = 44 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8y + 3y &= 44 \\\\\n11y &= 44 \\\\\n\\dfrac{11y}{11} &= \\dfrac{44}{11} \\\\\ny &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 44</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8y + 3y\\) if \\(y=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8y + 3y &= 8(4) + 3(4) \\\\\n&= 32 + 12 \\\\\n&= 44\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(36 = 13n - 4n \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n36 &= 13n - 4n \\\\\n36 &= 9n \\\\\n\\dfrac{36}{9} &= \\dfrac{9n}{9} \\\\\n4 &= n \\\\\nn &= 4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 36 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(13n - 4n\\) if \\(n=4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n13n - 4n &= 13(4) - 4(4) \\\\\n&= 52 - 16 \\\\\n&= 36 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(12y + 10y + 14 = 80 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n12y + 10y + 14 &= 80 \\\\\n22y + 14 &= 80 \\\\\n22y &= 80 - 14 \\\\\n22y &= 66 \\\\\n\\dfrac{22y}{22} &= \\dfrac{66}{22} \\\\\ny &= 3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 80</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(12y + 10y + 14\\) if \\(y=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n12y + 10y +14 &= 12(3) + 10(3) + 14 \\\\\n&= 36 + 30 + 14 \\\\\n&= 80\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6c - 8 - 2c = -16 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6c - 8 - 2c &= -16 \\\\\n6c - 2c &= -16 + 8 \\\\\n4c &= -8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4c}{4} &= \\dfrac{-8}{4} \\\\\nc &= -2 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -16</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6c - 8 - 2c\\) if \\(c=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6c - 8 - 2c &= 6(-2) - 8 - 2(-2) \\\\\n&= -12 - 8 - -4 \\\\\n&= -12 - 8 + 4 \\\\\n&= -16\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4(z + 5) = 32 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(z + 5) &= 32 \\\\\n4z + 20 &= 32 \\\\\n4z &= 32 - 20 \\\\\n4z &= 12 \\\\\n\\dfrac{4z}{4} &= \\dfrac{12}{4} \\\\\nz &= 3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 32</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(z + 5)\\) if \\(z=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(z + 5) &= 4(3 + 5) \\\\\n&= 4(8) \\\\\n&= 32\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2(4g - 3) = 30 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-2(4g - 3) &= 30 \\\\\n-8g + 6 &= 30 \\\\\n-8g &= 30 - 6 \\\\\n-8g &= 24 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-8g}{-8} &= \\dfrac{24}{-8} \\\\\ng &= -3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 30</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-2(4g - 3)\\) if \\(g=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-2(4g - 3) &= -2(4(-3) - 3) \\\\\n&= -2(-12 - 3) \\\\\n&= -2(-15) \\\\\n&= 30\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(6 + 5(m + 1) = 26 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6 + 5(m + 1) &= 26 \\\\\n6 +5m + 5 &= 26 \\\\\n5m &= 26 - 6 - 5 \\\\\n5m &= 15 \\\\\n\\dfrac{5m}{5} &= \\dfrac{15}{5} \\\\\nm &= 3 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 26</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6+5(m + 1)\\) if \\(m=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6 + 5(m + 1) &= 6 + 5(3 + 1) \\\\\n&= 6 + 5(4) \\\\\n&= 6 + 20 \\\\\n&= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5h + 2(11 - h) = -5 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5h + 2(11 - h) &= -5 \\\\\n5h +22 - 2h &= -5 \\\\\n5h - 2h &=  -5 - 22 \\\\\n3h &= -27 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3h}{3} &= \\dfrac{-27}{3} \\\\\nh &= -9 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -5</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5h+2(11 - h)\\) if \\(h=-9\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5h + 2(11 - h) &= 5(-9) + 2(11 - (-9)) \\\\\n&= -45 + 2(11 + 9) \\\\\n&= -45 + 2(20) \\\\\n&= -45 + 40 \\\\\n&= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(27 = 3c - 3(6 - 2c) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n27 &= 3c - 3(6 - 2c) \\\\\n27 &= 3c - 18 + 6c \\\\\n27 + 18 &=  3c + 6c \\\\\n45 &= 9c \\\\\n\\dfrac{45}{9} &= \\dfrac{9c}{9} \\\\\n5 &= c \\\\\nc &= 5 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 27= RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3c-3(6 - 2c)\\) if \\(c=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3c - 3(6 - 2c) &= 3(5) - 3(6 - 2(5)) \\\\\n&= 15 - 3(6 - 10) \\\\\n&= 15 - 3(-4) \\\\\n&= 15 + 12 \\\\\n&= 27\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3 = 12y - 5(2y - 7) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3 &= 12y - 5(2y - 7) \\\\\n-3 &= 12y - 10y + 35 \\\\\n-3  &=  2y + 35 \\\\\n-2y &= 35 + 3 \\\\\n-2y &= 38 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-2y}{-2} &= \\dfrac{38}{-2} \\\\\ny &= -19 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check -3 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(12y-5(2y - 7)\\) if \\(y=-19\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n12y - 5(2y - 7) &= 12(-19) - 5(2(-19) - 7) \\\\\n&= -228 - 5(-38 - 7) \\\\\n&= -228 - 5(-45) \\\\\n&= -228 + 225 \\\\\n&= -3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3(3 + x) + 4(x - 6) = -4 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3(3 + x) + 4(x - 6) &= -4 \\\\\n-9 - 3x + 4x - 24 &= -4 \\\\\n-3x + 4x  &=  -4 + 9 + 24 \\\\\nx &= 29 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = -4</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-3(3 + x) + 4(x - 6)\\) if \\(x=29\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3(3 + x) + 4(x - 6) &= -3(3 + 29) + 4(29 - 6) \\\\\n&= -3(32) + 4(23) \\\\\n&= -96 + 92 \\\\\n&= -4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5(r + 9) - 2(1 - r) = 1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5(r + 9) - 2(1 - r) &= 1 \\\\\n5r + 45 - 2 + 2r &= 1 \\\\\n5r + 2r  &=  1 - 45 +2 \\\\\n7r &= -42 \\\\\n\\dfrac{7r}{7} &= \\dfrac{-42}{7} \\\\\nr &= -6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 1</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5(r + 9) - 2(1 - r)\\) if \\(r=-6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5(r + 9) - 2(1 - r) &= 5(-6 + 9) - 2(1 - (-6)) \\\\\n&= 5(3) - 2(1 + 6) \\\\\n&= 15 - 2(7) \\\\\n&= 15 - 14 \\\\\n&= 1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(15 - 2x = 3x \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n15 - 2x &= 3x \\\\\n15 &= 3x + 2x \\\\\n15  &=  5x \\\\\n\\dfrac{15}{5} &= \\dfrac{5x}{5} \\\\\n3 &= x \\\\\nx &= 3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(15 - 2x\\) if \\(x=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n15 - 2x &= 15 - 2(3) \\\\\n&= 15 - 6 \\\\\n&= 9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3x\\) if \\(x=3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x &= 3(3) \\\\\n&= 9\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(26 - 4s = 9s \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n26 - 4s &= 9s \\\\\n26 &= 9s + 4s \\\\\n26 &=  13s \\\\\n\\dfrac{26}{13} &= \\dfrac{13s}{13} \\\\\n2 &= s \\\\\ns &= 2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(26 - 4s\\) if \\(s=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n26 - 4s &= 26 - 4(2) \\\\\n&= 26 - 8 \\\\\n&= 18\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(9s\\) if \\(s=2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n9s &= 9(2) \\\\\n&= 18\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5p - 9 = 2p + 12 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5p - 9 &= 2p + 12 \\\\\n5p - 2p &= 12 + 9 \\\\\n3p &=  21 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3p}{3} &= \\dfrac{21}{3} \\\\\np &= 7 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5p - 9\\) if \\(p=7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5p - 9 &= 5(7) - 9 \\\\\n&= 35 - 9 \\\\\n&= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2p + 12\\) if \\(p=7\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2p + 12 &= 2(7) + 12 \\\\\n&= 14 + 12 \\\\\n&= 26\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8g + 10 = 35 + 3g \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8g + 10 &= 35 + 3g \\\\\n8g - 3g &= 35 - 10 \\\\\n5g &=  25 \\\\\n\\dfrac{5g}{5} &= \\dfrac{25}{5} \\\\\ng &= 5 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(8g + 10\\) if \\(g=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8g + 10 &= 8(5) + 10 \\\\\n&= 40 + 10 \\\\\n&= 50\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(35 + 3g\\) if \\(g=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n35 + 3g &= 35 + 3(5) \\\\\n&= 35 + 15 \\\\\n&= 50\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5t + 16 = 6 - 5t \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5t + 16 &= 6 - 5t \\\\\n5t + 5t &= 6 - 16 \\\\\n10t &=  -10 \\\\\n\\dfrac{10t}{10} &= \\dfrac{-10}{10} \\\\\nt &= -1 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(5t + 16\\) if \\(t=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5t + 16 &= 5(-1) + 16 \\\\\n&= -5 + 16 \\\\\n&= 11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6 - 5t\\) if \\(t=-1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6 - 5t &= 6 - 5(-1) \\\\\n&= 6 + 5 \\\\\n&= 11\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-3r + 10 = 15r - 8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3r + 10 &= 15r - 8 \\\\\n-3r - 15r &= -8 - 10 \\\\\n-18r &=  -18 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-18r}{-18} &= \\dfrac{-18}{-18} \\\\\nr &= 1 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-3r + 10\\) if \\(r=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-3r + 10 &= -3(1) + 10 \\\\\n&= -3 + 10 \\\\\n&= 7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(15r - 8\\) if \\(r=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n15r - 8 &= 15(1) - 8 \\\\\n&= 15 - 8 \\\\\n&= 7\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + 3x - 12x = 3x + 1 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7 + 3x - 12x &= 3x + 1 \\\\\n7 - 1 &= 3x + 12x -3x \\\\\n6 &= 12x \\\\\n\\dfrac{6}{12} &= \\dfrac{12x}{12} \\\\\n\\frac{1}{2} &= x \\\\\nx &= \\frac{1}{2} \\text{ or } x = 0.5 \n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(7 + 3x  -  12x\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n7 + 3x  -  12x &= 7 + 3\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) -  12\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) \\\\\n&= 7 + \\dfrac{3}{2} - 6 \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{5}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(3x + 1\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n3x + 1 &= 3\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) + 1 \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{3}{2} + 1  \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{5}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(w - 2 + 2w = 6 + 5w \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nw - 2 + 2w &= 6 + 5w \\\\\nw + 2w - 5w  &= 6 + 2 \\\\\n-2w &= 8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-2w}{-2} &= \\dfrac{8}{-2} \\\\\nw &= -4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(w - 2  +  2w\\) if \\(w=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nw - 2  +  2w &= -4 - 2 + 2(-4) \\\\\n&= -6 + (-8) \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(6 + 5w\\) if \\(w=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n6 + 5w &= 6 + 5(-4) \\\\\n&= 6 - 20  \\\\\n&= -14\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10(g + 5) = 2(g + 9) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10(g + 5) &= 2(g + 9) \\\\\n10g + 50  &= 2g + 18 \\\\\n10g - 2g &= 18 - 50 \\\\\n8g &= -32 \\\\\n\\dfrac{8g}{8} &= \\dfrac{-32}{8} \\\\\ng &= -4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10(g  +  5)\\) if \\(g=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10(g + 5) &= 10(-4 + 5) \\\\\n&= 10(1) \\\\\n&= 10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(g + 9)\\) if \\(g=-4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(g + 9) &= 2(-4 + 9) \\\\\n&= 2(5)  \\\\\n&= 10\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9(t - 2) = 4(t - 15) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-9(t - 2) &= 4(t - 15) \\\\\n-9t + 18  &= 4t - 60 \\\\\n-9t - 4t &=  -60 - 18 \\\\\n-13t &= -78 \\\\\n\\dfrac{-13t}{-13} &= \\dfrac{-78}{-13} \\\\\nt &= 6\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-9(t  - 2)\\) if \\(t=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-9(t - 2) &= -9(6 - 2) \\\\\n&= -9(4) \\\\\n&= -36\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4(t - 15)\\) if \\(t=6\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4(t - 15) &= 4(6 - 15) \\\\\n&= 4(-9)  \\\\\n&= -36\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9) = -2(2x + 6) \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9) &= -2(2x + 6) \\\\\n3 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9)  &= 3 \\times -2(2x + 6) \\\\\n2(3x + 9) &=  -6(2x + 6) \\\\\n6x + 18 &= -12x - 36 \\\\\n6x + 12x &= -36 -18 \\\\\n18x &= -54 \\\\\n\\dfrac{18x}{18} &= \\dfrac{-54}{18} \\\\\nx &= -3\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9)\\) if \\(x=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{2}{3}(3x + 9) &= \\dfrac{2}{3}(3(-3) + 9) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{2}{3}(-9 + 9) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{2}{3}(0) \\\\\n&= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-2(2x + 6)\\) if \\(x=-3\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-2(2x + 6) &= -2(2(-3) + 6) \\\\\n&= -2(-6 + 6)  \\\\\n&= -2(0) \\\\\n&= 0\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(2t + 4) = \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)  \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(2t + 4) &= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)  \\\\\n4 \\times 2(2t + 4) &= 4 \\times \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)  \\\\\n8(2t + 4) &=  3(24 - 8t) \\\\\n16t + 32 &= 72 - 24t \\\\\n16t + 24t &= 72 - 32 \\\\\n40t &= 40 \\\\\n\\dfrac{40t}{40} &= \\dfrac{40}{40} \\\\\nt &= 1\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(2t + 4)\\) if \\(t=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(2t + 4) &= 2(2(1) + 4) \\\\\n&= 2(2 + 4) \\\\\n&= 2(6) \\\\\n&= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t)\\) if \\(t=1\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8t) &= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8(1)) \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24 - 8)  \\\\\n&= \\dfrac{3}{4}(16) \\\\\n&= 12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(10(2y + 2) - y = 2(8y - 8)  \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10(2y + 2) - y &= 2(8y - 8)  \\\\\n20y + 20 - y &= 16y - 16 \\\\\n20y - y - 16y &= -16 - 20 \\\\\n3y &= -36 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3y}{3} &= \\dfrac{-36}{3} \\\\\ny &= -12\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10(2y + 2) - y\\) if \\(y=-12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10(2y + 2) - y &= 10(2(-12) + 2) - (-12) \\\\\n&= 10(-24 + 2) + 12 \\\\\n&= 10(-22) + 12 \\\\\n&= -220 + 12\n&= -208\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(8y - 8)\\) if \\(y=-12\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(8y - 8) &= 2(8(-12) - 8) \\\\\n&= 2(-96 - 8)  \\\\\n&= 2(-104) \\\\\n&= -208\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2(4x + 2) = 4x - 12(x - 1)  \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(4x + 2) &= 4x - 12(x - 1)  \\\\\n8x + 4 &= 4x - 12x + 12 \\\\\n8x - 4x + 12x &= 12 - 4 \\\\\n16x &= 8 \\\\\n\\dfrac{16x}{16} &= \\dfrac{8}{16} \\\\\nx &= \\frac{1}{2}\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2(4x + 2)\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2(4x + 2) &= 2\\left(4\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) + 2\\right) \\\\\n&= 2(2 + 2) \\\\\n&= 2(4) \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(4x - 12(x - 1)\\) if \\(x=\\frac{1}{2}\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n4x - 12(x - 1) &= 4\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right) - 12\\left(\\dfrac{1}{2} - 1\\right) \\\\\n&= 2 - 12\\left(-\\dfrac{1}{2}\\right)  \\\\\n&= 2 - -6 \\\\\n&= 2 + 6 \\\\\n&= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(x+ 9 = 7 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx+ 9 &= 7 \\\\\nx &= 7 - 9 \\\\\nx &= -2\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 7</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(x + 9\\) if \\(x=-2\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nx + 9 &= -2 + 9 \\\\\n&= 7 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8.6 = z - 3.8 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n8.6 &= z - 3.8 \\\\\n8.6 + 3.8 &= z \\\\\n12.4 &= z \\\\\nz &= 12.4\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 8.6 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(z - 3.8\\) if \\(z=12.4\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\nz - 3.8 &= 12.4 - 3.8 \\\\\n&= 8.6 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(60 = -12r \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n60 &= -12r \\\\\n\\dfrac{60}{-12} &= \\dfrac{-12r}{-12} \\\\\n-5 &= r \\\\\nr &= -5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 60 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(-12r\\) if \\(r=-5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n-12r &= -12(-5) \\\\\n&= 60 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4}p = 18 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{4}p &= 18 \\\\\n4 \\times \\dfrac{3}{4}p &= 4 \\times 18 \\\\\n3p &= 72 \\\\\n\\dfrac{3p}{3} &= \\dfrac{72}{3} \\\\\np &= 24\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 18</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(\\dfrac{3}{4}p\\) if \\(p=24\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n\\dfrac{3}{4}p &= \\dfrac{3}{4}(24) \\\\\n&= 18 \\\\\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2m - 3 = 13 \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2m - 3 &= 13 \\\\\n2m &= 13 + 3 \\\\\n2m &= 16 \\\\\n\\dfrac{2m}{2} &= \\dfrac{16}{2} \\\\\nm &= 8\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check LHS = 13</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(2m - 3\\) if \\(m=8\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n2m - 3 &= 2(8) - 3 \\\\\n&= 16 - 3 \\\\\n&= 13\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 = 10 - v \\)",
      "answer": "\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n5 &= 10 - v \\\\\nv &= 10 - 5 \\\\\nv &= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]\n\n<div>Check 5 = RHS</div>\n\n<div>Evaluate \\(10 - v\\) if \\(v=5\\)</div>\n\n\\[\n\\begin{align*}\n10 - v &= 10 - 5 \\\\\n&= 5\n\\end{align*}\n\\]"
    }
  ]
}
